They aren't just shoes
Kicks is a drama, crime, action film directed by Justin Tipping.
When his hard-earned kicks get snatched by a local hood, fifteen-year old Brandon and his two best
friends go on an ill-advised mission across the Bay Area to retrieve the stolen sneakers.
Brandon, played by Jahking Guillory.
Flaco, played by Kofi Siriboe.
Marlon, played by Mahershala Ali.
Rico, played by Christopher Meyer.
Albert, played by C.J. Wallace.
The Astronaut, played by Molly Shaiken.
Kicks is a 2016 American adventure film directed by Justin Tipping in his
directorial debut, and written by Tipping and Joshua Beirne-Golden.
The film stars Jahking Guillory, Christopher Jordan Wallace, Christopher
Meyer, Kofi Siriboe, Mahershala Ali and Molly Shaiken.
The film was released on September 9, 2016, by Focus World.
The film explores themes of cigarette, blow job,
pot smoking, shoe, illegal drugs.
The tone is emotional.